(whirring)
(gentle music)
♪ Maybe it's intuition ♪
♪ But some things you
just don't question ♪
♪ Like in your eyes, I see
my future in an instant ♪
♪ And there it goes ♪
♪ I think I found my best friend ♪
♪ I know that it might sound ♪
♪ More than a little crazy but I believe ♪
♪ I knew I loved you before I met you ♪
♪ I think I dreamed you into life ♪
♪ I have been waiting all my life ♪
♪ There's just no rhyme or reason ♪
♪ Only the sense of completion ♪
♪ And in your eyes ♪
♪ I see the missing
pieces I'm searching for ♪
♪ I think I've found my way home ♪
♪ I know that it might sound ♪
♪ More than a little crazy but I believe ♪
♪ I knew I loved you before I met you ♪
♪ I think I dreamed you into life ♪
♪ I have been waiting all my life ♪
♪ A thousand angels dance around you ♪
♪ I am complete now that I've found you ♪
♪ I knew I loved you before I met you ♪
♪ I think I dreamed you into life ♪
♪ I have been waiting all my life ♪
♪ I knew I loved you before I met you ♪
♪ I knew I loved you ♪
♪ I knew I loved you
before I met you, yeah ♪
♪ I knew I loved you ♪